<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Zuperb</title>
    <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Zuperb</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:03:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zuperb.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#3 The Logo</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/3-the-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:03:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/3-the-logo/</guid>
      <description>Pssshh: Adobe firefly generated it 😉 I love these kind of tools - amazing!&#xA;I actually wanted some meaningful logo like the YinYang, etc.&#xA;But this one is good as a version 1 logo - looks pretty pretty in my opinion. Do you like it? 👆&#xA;Tomorrow if I get time, I will move these posts to new blog at zuperb.in&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s it for today, wishing you a great day!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#2 Finding a Zuperb Name</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/2-finding-a-zuperb-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:00:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/2-finding-a-zuperb-name/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Finding a name, getting website for this project.&#xA;Intro This endeavor/project/website needs a name.&#xA;People say naming is difficult. Very true, I felt, for this project. Read Part 1 to get an idea why.&#xA;Life has infinitely many facets. A project that&amp;rsquo;s about life should also have a name like &amp;rsquo;life&#39;.&#xA;Fun exercise: try creating a word like &amp;rsquo;life&#39;.&#xA;The immediate reason why a name is required I want to put these posts/logs in some place, a website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#1 A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/1-a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/1-a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Summary: &amp;ldquo;Post on a new beginning in my life. Building something in public that is aimed at making life better.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Intro (hype) This marks the beginning of a new phase in my life.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m going to build something in public. This is something that is coming out through me I feel, more than I creating it. This is an idea whose time has come, it looks like.&#xA;Let me search and get that proverb that says the same&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
