<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Zuperb</title>
    <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Zuperb</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:40:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zuperb.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#8 Hello Clojure</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/8-hello-clojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:40:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/8-hello-clojure/</guid>
      <description>Summary Learning Clojure Syntax&#xA;Going the functional route I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching Rich Hickey talking about Clojure ideas, Datomic, etc. after the last post. He is a charismatic speaker, no question about it. But more than his charisma and persuasion, the ideas themselves are impressive. Simple in the real sense, I felt. There is a certain elegance, clarity and sanity in the functional world I feel. Less magic. Okay. Let&amp;rsquo;s go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#7 Let us try Clojure</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/7-lets-choose-clojure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:27:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/7-lets-choose-clojure/</guid>
      <description>Summary Not spending enough time these days due to other things I&amp;rsquo;m involved in. Going for Functional programming/Clojure for Zuperb.&#xA;What&amp;rsquo;s happening? It&amp;rsquo;s been a couple of days since I last sat down for Zuperb. Pop and Mom are in town. They staying with my sister, but I&amp;rsquo;m visiting them in the evenings after work. There&amp;rsquo;s also a workation coming up - to Munnar on Friday. So I&amp;rsquo;ll be away from Zuperb for a couple more days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#6 Exploring Programming Paradigms</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/6-exploring-programming-paradigms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 21:52:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/6-exploring-programming-paradigms/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Checking out some ideas on how to code well&#xA;Indecision In the last one, I had resolved to build the backend for Zuperb in two frameworks - Flask and NestJS. After that, I was thinking Express is better than NestJS. I think I&amp;rsquo;m swinging between &amp;lsquo;batteries-included&amp;rsquo; so that I can quickly build things vs. &amp;lsquo;bare-bones&amp;rsquo; so that I can have more control and not carry things I don&amp;rsquo;t need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#5 Mindstream -&gt; Paper -&gt; Bits</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/5-trying-mind-to-paper-to-bits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:21:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/5-trying-mind-to-paper-to-bits/</guid>
      <description>Summary Streamed thoughts about how to proceed with the project onto paper - 5 sheets. Transcribed them (converted to text) with the help of ChatGPT. Edited a little bit, fixed a few errors, added headings, etc. Too long; maybe don&amp;rsquo;t read! Okay, my mind says: I will start off writing what I thought last: &amp;ldquo;keep moving.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Because my father and mother are both teachers&amp;hellip; Wait a minute, not because they are teachers, maybe because of their teaching style&amp;hellip; Hmm, now when I think about it, it&amp;rsquo;s not just in teaching, it&amp;rsquo;s a general psychological thing - &amp;ldquo;Pointing out mistakes, imperfections, flaws, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#4 Creating A Zuperb Blog</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/4-creating-zuperb-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:09:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/4-creating-zuperb-blog/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Moving the posts from blogspot to hugo site hosted in Github pages at zuperb.in&#xA;What next? So, we have a name for this, a domain for the website.&#xA;Next, we&amp;rsquo;ll move these posts from blogspot to that web address.&#xA;Plan For that, we need to:&#xA;put these posts in a place connect the domain zuperb.in with that place of hosting The site generator - Hugo The posts need to also look like a blog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3 The Logo</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/3-the-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:36:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/3-the-logo/</guid>
      <description>Pssshh: Adobe firefly generated it 😉 I love these kind of tools - amazing!&#xA;I actually wanted some meaningful logo like the YinYang, etc.&#xA;But this one is good as a version 1 logo - looks pretty pretty in my opinion. Do you like it? 👆&#xA;Also got a favicon created from it thanks to https://realfavicongenerator.net/favicon_result?file_id=p1i096r2vmk51kje15ga2ndkl76&#xA;Tomorrow if I get time, I will move these posts to new blog at zuperb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#2 Finding a Zuperb Name</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/2-finding-a-zuperb-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/2-finding-a-zuperb-name/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Finding a name, getting website for this project.&#xA;Intro This endeavor/project/website needs a name.&#xA;People say naming is difficult. Very true, I felt, for this project. Read Part 1 to get an idea why.&#xA;Life has infinitely many facets. A project that&amp;rsquo;s about life should also have a name like &amp;rsquo;life&#39;.&#xA;Fun exercise: try creating a word like &amp;rsquo;life&#39;.&#xA;The immediate reason why a name is required I want to put these posts/logs in some place, a website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#1 A New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://zuperb.in/posts/1-a-new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:47:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zuperb.in/posts/1-a-new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>Summary: &amp;ldquo;Post on a new beginning in my life. Building something in public that is aimed at making life better.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Intro (hype) This marks the beginning of a new phase in my life.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m going to build something in public. This is something that is coming out through me I feel, more than I creating it. This is an idea whose time has come, it looks like.&#xA;Let me search and get that proverb that says the same&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
